# Luke Lovekin

Full-Stack Developer Jnr



+61424480638



/lukelovekin



/lukelovekin



<u>Portfolio</u>



lukelovekin@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

My goal is to gain experience in technical skills and industry processes. I have a new found passion for Web/Software Development and I'm very excited to see where it take me. I'm confident my previous work as a Site Supervisor has provided me with similar core concepts that I can use when working as a Developer and to progress naturally as I develop more technical skills. Although I'm fairly new to the industry, I am experienced in managing large groups of people on projects start to finish while keeping everyone on time, on budget, safe, following quality expectations and following Australian Regulations all while constantly solving problems and managing delays and defects.

When I'm not coding my hobbies include exercising with my dog, gaming, AFL, socialising, renovating and always working towards something new and challenging.

# **Projects**

# Scrunch - Internship - Flutter, Firebase

Interning as a software Engineer, working on a mobile app that aims to improve personal well being through and AI companion that motivates the user.

Roles: Passwordless Login, Testing, Landing Page flow, In code documentation, ...still in progress

#### Coder Academy - MERN Stack - FreeSpace

A free tier webpage for artist to host their portfolios on https://github.com/lukelovekin/FreeSpace-CA-MERN-Project https://free-space.gq/https://free-space-api.herokuapp.com/

## Coder Academy - Hackathon - Ruby on Rails

Two classmates and I created a Coder Academy Cohort forum, using Github authorisation students can post topics, comments and photos. 4 day time limit

http://codr.academy/

https://github.com/chambost/codr.academy-rails

# Coder Academy - Cars4Ads - Ruby on Rails

Two sided marketplace bringing introducing car owners to business advertisements. 2 week time limit

https://cars4ads.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/lukelovekin/LukeLovekin\_T2A2

## Coder Academy - Terminal Application - Ruby

A CLI application with a focus to fulfil duties that of a property manager. 1 week time limit

https://github.com/lukelovekin/terminal-app-property-manager

# Coder Academy - Portfolio (OLD) - HTML and CSS only

A responsive accessible portfolio about myself created using only HTML and CSS. 1 week time limit https://github.com/lukelovekin/portfolio1-html-css-only (old)

https://lukelovekin.github.io/portfolio/ (new portfolio)

## References

References can be provided upon request

#### Skills

Experience with:

- Javascript
- Dart
- MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.Js)
- HTML5, CSS3/ SCSS
- Ruby on Rails
- Version Control (Github)
- Agile Methodology (Trello)
- PostgreSQL, AWS S3, Heroku, Bootstrap
- Positive and Optimistic
- Adaptable with Ability to Learn Quick.
- Leadership and Influence Qualities
- Proactive Problem Solver
- Communication and Collaboration
- Reliabe Teamworker with the ability to work Autonomously.

#### Education

# Coder Academy Brisbane

Diploma of Information & Technology 2020 - 2020

#### **Mountain Creek**

High School 2005 - 2009

## **Employment History**

#### Site Supervisor | For Her Construction | 2015 - 2020

- Managing the overall site performance of construction processes
- Maximising site production by ensuring sub contract trade availability
- -Continuously reviewing building practices and procedures
- Ensuring compliance with and delivery of established cost management and project management practices
- Fostering a positive and focused culture where customer service and teamwork is paramount.
- Strong project management skills, knowledge of building regulations, OHS regulations.
- Experience in developing and managing organisational and external networks, particularly with trades  $\,$
- Customer focus, communication and conflict resolution skills
- The ability to communicate professionally, prioritise and meet deadlines
- -Implement a high level of attention to detail and a proactive approach to all tasks undertaken.

# Carpenter | Tim Unsted Building | 2010 - 2015

- Support site safety and honest work ethics
- Studying drawings and specifications to determine materials required
- Dimensions and installation procedures
- Verifying trueness of structures
- Assembling prepared wood to form structures and fittings ready to install
- Construct concrete formwork

#### Achievements

- Top 20 most money fundraised for MND and Me
- Gold Coast Marathon